Guide to the Jerome H. Holland papers, 1953-1985
Holland, Jerome H. papers, 1953-1985
- Series I. Professional Files
  - Cornell University: Jerome H. Holland International Living Center, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Cornell University: Miscellaneous, 1937-1939 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Cornell University: National Corporate Gift Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Cornell University: Joseph N. Pew, Jr. Engineering Professorship, 1946-1957 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Cornell University: Remarks at Alumni Assembly, June 15, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Cornell University: Student Demonstrations, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Cornell University: 3rd Annual Mid-Fifties Class Dinner, April 24, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Cornell University: Tower Club, 1968-1969, 1973, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Cornell University: Trustee and Cornell Alumni Association addresses, 1979-1985 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Cornell University: Wilhelhm Weinberg Labor-Management Public Interest Seminar, November 12, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Council for Advancement and Support of Education (C.A.S.E.), 1976-1984 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Council of Concerned Black Executives, Inc., 1976-1978, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1977-1984 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Crank letters, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Crispus Attucks Annual Award Night, May 9, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Culbro Corporation, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Culbro Corporation, 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Culbro Corporation, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Culbro Corporation: Audit Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Culbro Corporation: Audit Committee, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Culbro Corporation: Machine Systems, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Culbro Corporation: Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Culbro Corporation: Public policy, 1977-1983 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Cummings Memorial Fund Trust, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Curry, Pamela Holland, 1975-1983 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - D: General, 1944-1969 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - D: General, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - D: General, 1974-May 1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - D: General, June 1975-July 1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - D: General, Sept. 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - D: General, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Daily Progress, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - De Young Press, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Delaware State College: Caribbean and International Club, April-June 1960 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Delaware State College: Correspondence, 1953-1964 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Delaware State College: Correspondence, 1972-1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Delaware State College: Dinner honoring President Jerome H. Holland, May 6, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Delaware State College: Eighty-Ninth Annual Commencement, December 1980-June 1981 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Delaware State College: Eighty-Seventh Founders Day Program, February 5, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Delaware State College: Miscellaneous, 1950-1961, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Delaware State College: Speeches, 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Delaware State College: Speeches, 1956-1958 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Detroit Personnel Management Association, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Dewey, Thomas E., 1945 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Dillard University, January-March 1976 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Diners Club, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Doke, Teri Y., 1973-1982 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Donlon, Mary H., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Donovan, Frank: Correspondence about Black Opportunity, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - DuPonts: Personal corrspondence, 1961-1969 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Dynamismm (Kahlman Linker), 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - E: General, 1961-1962, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - E: General, 1974-1983 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company, 1945-1964 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Eastern Michigan University, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Eberstadt, F. and Company, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Eberstadt, F. and Company, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Eberstadt, F. and Company: Surveyor Fund, Inc., 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Ebony, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Economic Club of Detroit, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Economic Development Council of New York City: Health and Hospitals Corporation Committee, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, 1977-1984 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Education Alumni Association, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Engagements, 1953-1957 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Engagements, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Engagements, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Engagements, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Entertainments, 1953-1956 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Europe-America Conference, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Executive Report, vol. 1, no. 2, December 1978 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Expenditures, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Experiment in International Living, 1962-1967 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Experiment in International Living, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Experiment in International Living, 1972-1984 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Exum, Alex, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - F: General, 1950-June 1973 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - F: General, July 1973-Aug. 1976 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - F: General, Sept. 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Family Service Association, 1977-1983 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Fan mail, 1972-1984 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Farm Journal, Inc., August-September 1952 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Farm Labor Program, 1944-1946, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Federated Department Stores, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Federated Department Stores, Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Federated Department Stores, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Federated Department Stores, Inc., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Federated Department Stores, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Federated Department Stores, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Federated Department Stores, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Federated Department Stores, Inc.: Audit Committee, 1974-1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Federated Department Stores, Inc.: Executives deferred compensation plan, 1978-1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Federated Department Stores, Inc.: Nominating Committee, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Fellowship Commission and Fellowship House, December 1952-August 1953 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 52 Association, Inc., 1982 Medal of Honor, 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - First Harlem Securities, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Fisk University, 1945, 1960-1962 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Foote, Robert, 1967-1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Ford, Gerald, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1972-1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1977-1983 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Fort Valley State College, Georgia, August 1956 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Foundations, May-Oct. 1954 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Foundations, Nov. 1954-Sept. 1955 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Foundations, Nov. 1955-Nov. 1956 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Foundations, Dec. 1956-June 1958 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Foundations, July 1958-1962 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge, 1962-1970 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge, 1972-1983 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Freeman, Dr. W. Adrian, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Friends of the Stockholm Philharmonic, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Frontiers International, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - G: General, 1944-1973 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - G: General, 1974-1977 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - G: General, 1978-1984 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - General Foods Corporation: Ad Hoc Committee on Refocusing General Food's Contributions, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - General Foods Corporation: Address to Executives, October 6, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - General Foods Corporation: Annual Report, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - General Foods Corporation: Audit Committee, 1978-1983 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - General Foods Corporation: Board of Directors Meeting Agenda, October 1983 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - General Foods Corporation: Board of Directors minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - General Foods Corporation: Correspondence, 1969-1974 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - General Foods Corporation: Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - General Foods Corporation: Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - General Foods Corporation: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - General Foods Corporation: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - General Foods Corporation: Deferred compensation, 1973, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - General Foods Corporation: European trip, October 2-6, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - General Foods Corporation: European trip, October 2-6, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - General Foods Corporation: Law Department Address, April-May 1980 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - General Foods Corporation: Nominating Committee, 1978-1983 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - General Foods Corporation: Oscar Mayer & Co., 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - General Foods Corporation: Photographs and Miscellaneous, 1980-1983, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - General Foods Corporation: Retirement Plan Committee, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - General Foods Corporation: U.K.-Germany Trip, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - General Foods Fund, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Glenmede Trust Company: Allyn R. Bell, Jr., 1958-1961 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Glenmede Trust Company: Allyn R. Bell, Jr., 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Glenmede Trust Company: Allyn R. Bell, Jr., 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Glenmede Trust Company: Robert I. Smith, 1973-1983 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Green Beret Holding Company, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - H: General, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Hamilton, Alexander Institute, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Hammond, Roxana and family, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Hampton Institute: Carnegie Corporation trips, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Hampton Institute: Correspondence, 1942-1960 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Hampton Institute: Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Hampton Institute: Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Hampton Institute: Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Hampton Institute: Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Hampton Institute: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Hampton Institute: Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Hampton Institute: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Hampton Institute: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Hampton Institute: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Hampton Institute: Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Hampton Institute: Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Hampton Institute: Germany Trip, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Hampton Institute: Inauguration, November 1960 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Hampton Institute: Inauguration, Jan.-April 1961 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Hampton Institute: Inauguration, May 1-4, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Hampton Institute: Inauguration, May 5, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Hampton Institute: Inauguration, May 8-12, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Hampton Institute: Inauguration, May 15-Sept. 1961, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Hampton Institute: Inauguration clippings, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Hampton Institute: Inauguration speeches, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Hampton Institute: "A Mirror of Hope" President's Five Year Report, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Hampton Institute: President's Discretionary Fund, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Hampton Institute: Resignation, September 1969 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Hampton Institute: Resignation, Oct.-Dec. 1969 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Hampton Institute: Speeches, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Hampton Institute: Speeches, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Hampton Institute: Speeches, 1962-1964 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Hampton Institute: Speeches, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Hampton Institute: Speeches, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Hampton Institute: Speeches, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Hampton Institute: Speeches, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Harriman, E. Roland, 1966-1970 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Hazen Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Hilaael, Timothy M., 1972-1975 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Hobart and William Smith Colleges, October 1965 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Hobart and William Smith Colleges, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Employment Information, 1975-1979 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, 1938-1942 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, 1945, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, 1946-1948 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, Jan.-July 1953 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, Aug.-Oct. 1953 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, Nov.-Dec. 1953 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, Jan.-June 1954 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, July 1954-June 1955 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, July 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, 1957-April 1958 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, May 1958-1960 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, January-June 1961 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, July-Dec. 1961 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, January-August 1964 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, Sept. 1964-Dec. 1965 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, Feb.-Dec. 1969 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, January-June 1973 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, July-Dec. 1973 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, January-April 1974 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, May-Dec. 1974 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, Jan.-June 1975 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, July 1975-Feb. 1976 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, March-Dec. 1976 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, 1983-April 1984 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, May-June 1984 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, July-August 1984 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal, Sept. 1984-Jan. 1985 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Personal charity and philanthropy, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Physical education building, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Special awards, 1957-1959 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Holland, Jerome H.: Vita (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Holmes, Lucky, 1973, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Holyoke, Massachusettes Area Chamber of Commerce, July-October 1974 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Hoover Institute on War, Revolution and Peace, 1973-1979 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - I: General, 1953-1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Agriculture Summer Program: Applicants/Job offers, November 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Agriculture Summer Program: Applicants/Job offers 2, November 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Agriculture Summer Program: Curtis Brothers Company, November 1945-1953 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Industrial Agriculture Summer Program: General, November 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Industrial Agriculture Summer Program: General Foods, Birds Eye-Snider Division, November 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Industrial Agriculture Summer Program: New York Frozen Foods Corp., July 1946-Feb. 1947 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Industrial Agriculture Summer Program: Program Review, November 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Industrial Agriculture Summer Program: Recruiting, November 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Industrial Agriculture Summer Program: Recruiting 2, November 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Industrial Agriculture Summer Program: Recruiting 3, November 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Industrial Agriculture Summer Program: General, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Industrial Race Relations Commission, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Institute of International Education, 1973-1982 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - International Business Machine, 1961-1984 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity, 1973-1974, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Investor Responsibility Research Center, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Iran trip, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - J: General, 1960-1983, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Jessie Smith Noyes Foundation, 1952-1953 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Johnson, Lady Bird, November 1981 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Johnson Foundation, 1972-June 1973 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Johnson Foundation, July 1973-Feb. 1974 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Johnson Foundation, Mar. 1974-Feb. 1975 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Johnson Foundation, Mar.ch-Dec. 1975 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Johnson Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Johnson Foundation, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Johnson Foundation, 1981-May 1983 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Johnson Foundation, June 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Johnson, S. C. & Son, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Johnson, S. C. & Son, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Johnson, S. C. & Son, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Johnson, S. C. & Son, 1982-May 1983 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Johnson, S. C. & Son, June 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Johnson, S. C. & Son, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Johnson, S. C. & Son: Social Responsibility Task Force report, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Johnson, S. C. & Son: Trips to France, 1978-1984 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Johnson Wax Fund, 1974-1985 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Johnson Wax Global Conference: "Excellence & Beyond", September 15-21, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Johnson Wax Global Conference: "Knowing...Feeling...Being", November 8-14, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Johnson Wax Global Conference: "This We Believe" program, Apr.-July 1980 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Johnson Wax Global Conference: "This We Believe" program, Aug. 1980 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Johnson Wax Global Conference: "This We Believe" program, Sept.-Nov. 1980 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Johnson Wax: San Salvador trip, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Jones, Howard, 1974-1979 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Jones, Reginald-General Electric, 1973, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Journal of Negro Education, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - J.P. Stevens and Company, 1974-1984 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - K: General, 1952-1980 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Kane, Robert J.: Testimonial dinner and fund, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Kellems Company, June-Sept. 1945 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Kendall Company, 1976, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Kenyon College, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Kissinger, Henry A., 1973 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Kittrell, Dr. Flemmie P., 1974, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Kittrell, Dr. Flemmie P., October 1980 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Kittrell, Dr. Flemmie P.: Remarks at Testimonial Dinner honoring Dr. Kitrell, March 13, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Kiwanis Club of San Diego, Spirit of America, March-May 1976 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Knoxville College, 1959-1962, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Ladd, Kate Macy Fund, 1952, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Ladd, Kate Macy Fund, 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Ladd, Kate Macy Fund, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Ladd, Kate Macy Fund, 1957-1960 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - L: General, 1947-1984 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Lambert Trophies Board, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Le Moyne College, 1959-1963 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Lehman Brothers, Inc., 1973-1983 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Leopold Schepp Foundation, 1942-1944, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Liberty Bowl Festival Association, Nov.-Dec. 1977, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Lincoln University, Pennsylvania, 1942-1953 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Lincoln University, Pennsylvania, 1959-1973, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Lincoln University, Pennsylvania: Chapel Speech "Our Challenging Times", April 1, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Livingstone College, 1959-1963 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - M: General, 1951-1984 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust, 1972-July 1973 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust, Aug. 1973-Aug. 1974 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust, Sept. 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust, 1978-1980 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust: Brazil trip, May 13-20, 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust: Examining Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust: Hong Kong-Manila trip, May 6-20, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust: London trip, June 16-17, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust: Retirement plan, 1974-1978 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust: Retirement plan, 1981-1984 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust: Retirement plan financial statements, 1976-1984 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Marcos, President and Mrs. Ferdinand, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Marine Corps. Scholarship Foundation, Inc., 1979 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Mason and Company, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Jan.-June 1978 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, July 1978-1983 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Athletics, 1974-1981 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Humanities Visiting Committee, 1972-Jan. 1974 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Humanities Visiting Committee, Feb.-Oct. 1974 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Humanities Visiting Committee, Nov. 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Humanities Visiting Committee minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Visiting Committee, 1976-1982 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Members of the Corporation, 1974-1975, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Presentation at Annual Banquet of the Athletic Association, May 15, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Medgar Evers College, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Meharry Medical College, 1955-1980 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Middle Atlantic Placement Association, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1960, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976-1983 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Mobile Oil Corporation, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Mobile Oil Corporation, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Mobile Oil Corporation, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 11)